Finding Aid for the Norman Maurer Papers PASC.0086
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Script material
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/20/1980 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/6/1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    CANINE TO FIVE -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/7/1980 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    CHINESE FOOD FACTORY (THE) - REVISED VERSION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/7/1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    EXCALIBUR SCOOBY - FIRST DRAFT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/12/1980 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    FUTURE FREAKS - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/21/1981 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    GOOD (THE) BAD (A)ND THE SCOOBY (THE) - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/28/1980 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    HANG IN THERE SCOOBY! -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/24/1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    HARD HAT SCOOBY - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/17/1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/29/1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    LIGHTHOUSE KEEPER SCOOBY - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/23/1980 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    LONG JOHN SCRAPPY.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/28/1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    LOST FORBIDDEN GOLD MINE (THE) - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/8/1980 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    MUMMY'S THE WORD - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/16/1980 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    OLD CAT AND MOUSE GAME (THE) - FIRST DRAFT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/4/1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    PIGSKIN SCOOBY -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/8/1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    PUNK ROCK SCOOBY - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/28/1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    RICKSHAW SCOOBY - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 3/24/1980 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    ROCK AROUND THE LOCH! - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/13/1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    SCOOBY AND THE BEANSTALK - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/3/1981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    SCOOBY AT OCEANWORLD - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/6/1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    SCOOBY DOO 2000! - THREE SCRIPTS, TWO REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/20/1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/22/1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    SCOOBY-NOCCHIO - TWO SCRIPTS, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/27/1980 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    SCOOBY'S BULL FRIGHT - FIRST DRAFT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 4/23/1980 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    SCOOBY'S DESERT DILEMMA - SECOND REVISION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/8/1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/19/1980 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    SCOOBY'S FANTASTIC ISLAND - FIRST DRAFT.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/22/1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    SCOOBY'S HOUSE OF MYSTERY - REVISED VERSION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/5/1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    SCOOBY'S LUCK OF THE IRISH - ORIGINAL AND TWO REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/7/1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    SCOOBY'S ROOTS - COMPLETE REVISION.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/24/1981 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    SCOOBY'S SEA LAND/SEAWEED SCOOBY/LONG TIME NO SEAW - PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/20/1980 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    SCOOBY'S THREE DINGALING CIRCUS - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 8/5/1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    SOPWITH SCOOBY - TWO DIFFERENT VERSIONS AND PREMISE.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/2/1980 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    STOW-AWAYS - ASSORTED COPIES.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 5/13/1980 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 6/18/1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    SWEET DREAMS SCOOBY - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SCOOBY AND SCRAPPY DOO, 7/22/1981 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    TENDERBIGFOOT - PREMISE.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/15/1981 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    AEROGUE - PREMISE.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/4/1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    AIRCRAFT TERROR (THE) - OUTLINE AND SCRIPT.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/14/1981 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    ALIEN MUMMY -TWO DIFFERENT COPIES.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/20/1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    AROUND THE WORLD IN EIGHTY RIDDLES - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 8/10/1981 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    BAZAROWURLD - PREMISE AND TWO DIFFERENT VERSIONS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/7/1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    BIGFOOT - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/15/1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    CIRCUS OF HORRORS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/15/1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    COLOSSUS - OUTLINE AND SCRIPT.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/19/1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/28/1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    DIVE TO DISASTER - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    ERUPTION - REVISED VERSION.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/12/1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    EVIL FROM KRYPTON (THE) - FOUR COPIES, THREE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/23/1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    GARDEN OF DOOM.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/28/1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    HAUNTED HOUSE - ONE REVISED COPY, ONE FINAL.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/28/1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    ICE DEMON (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/2/1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    INCREDIBLE CRUDE OIL MONSTER (THE).
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/6/1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    INVASION OF THE GLEEKS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/11/1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    IRON CYCLOPS (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    KILLER MACHINES (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    MAKE-UP MONSTER (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/20/1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    MAN IN THE MOON (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/1/1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    MXYZPTLK STRIKES AGAIN - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/25/1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    MXYZPTLK'S FLICK - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/4/1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/17/1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/29/1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    PAULETTE'S PERILS - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    RETURN OF ATLANTIS - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    REVENGE OF BIZARRO - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 4/28/1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    ROCK 'N' ROLL SPACE BANDITS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/8/1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    SCARAGHOSTA SEA (THE) - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/2/1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    SCORPIO - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/8/1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    SINK HOLE -TWO DIFFERENT REVISIONS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/31/1981 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    STOWAWAYS FROM SPACE - PREMISE AND TWO VERSIONS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    TERMITES FROM VENUS - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/27/1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/3/1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    VOODOO VAMPIRE.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 6/23/1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    WARLORD'S AMULET (THE) - SCRIPTS,OUTLINE,REVISIONS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 7/23/1981 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    WITCH'S ARCADE (THE) - THREE VERSIONS.
  - SUPER FRIENDS, 5/2/1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    YUNA THE TERRIBLE - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - TEEN HULK, 12/17/1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 6/23/1980 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    ATTACK OF THE WARRIOR WOMEN - REVISED VERSION.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/5/1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    CITY OF EVIL - TWO COPIES, DIFFERENT DATES.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 10/24/1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    DEVELOPMENT FOR SATURDAY MORNING TELEVISION - TWO COPIES, ONE WITH NOTES.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/6/1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    FORTRESS OF FEAR - REVISED VERSION.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 4/30/1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    HARVEST OF DOOM - REVISED SCRIPTS AND OUTLINE.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 4/16/1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    ISLAND OF THE BODYSNATCHERS - REVISED VERSION.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/18/1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    LAST TRAIN TO DOOMSDAY - REVISED VERSION.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 6/8/1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    MASTER OF THE STOLEN SUNSWORD - REVISED VERSION.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/21/1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    MINDOK THE MIND MASTER - TWO COPIES, ONE REVISED.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 4/21/1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    PERIL FROM THE PAST (THE) - REVISED OUTLINE AND SCRIPTS.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 6/22/1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    PROPHECY OF PERIL - FIRST DRAFT.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/12/1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    RAIDERS OF THE ABYSS - REVISED OUTLINE AND SCRIPTS.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 12/26/1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    SECRET OF THE BLACK PEARL - PILOT.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 5/16/1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    TREASURE OF THE MOKS - REVISED SCRIPT AND OUTLINE.
  - THUNDARR THE BARBARIAN, 4/6/1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    WIZARD WAR! - TWO REVISED COPIES.